=The Outlaw=
(This story is entirely fictional.)
(All settings are imaginary.)
=Episode 17=
And I'm here today
to solve this problem for everyone.
Oh, perfect timing.
Let's welcome my new partner.
Mian.
You again.
Everyone.
I'll say just one thing.
Ms. Layla has my full support.
If you support Ms. Layla,
the Songcai family's business
is under my protection.
Otherwise,
the Songcai family
won't exist in Langia anymore.
We were worried
Mr. Natuo and Mian
would turn against each other.
We didn't know how the group
would move forward.
That's a relief.
Since
Mr. Mian is willing to help,
things will be much easier.
Exactly.
Good.
Let's vote, then.
Those who support
the family head's motion,
raise your hands.
Go ahead.
I dare you!
Alright.
The board has voted unanimously.
Natuo.
As of today,
I'm the new president
of the Songcai Group.
This mine
is mine now.
You actually played me?
What's the rush?
The game just started.
Your money.
Your power.
Everyone around you.
I'll take them away, one by one.
When you have nothing left,
you'll finally know
what it means
to wish you were dead.
In your dreams.
Fine.
You...
Just wait and see.
Ms. Layla.
I did
what I promised you.
Thank you, Mr. Mian.
I won't forget
what I promised you, either.
I look forward to working
with all of you.
Get over here, all of you!
I'm taking Mian down now.
Got it.
Let's go.
Move!
Go!
Natuo.
What are you doing?
Today,
I'll show you all
who's tougher,
me or Mian.
You're out of your league.
Get them!
Get over here, now!
These guys
are trying to take my mine.
Kill them all!
Anyone who won't fight,
look at those dead men from last night.
That's your fate.
Mian.
Today,
I'll send you to your grave.
Boss.
Let's fight them!
Don't turn on each other.
We've all suffered in this mine.
Think how many of your
closest brothers
that monster killed last night.
♪Dust rises along the border♪
Pick them up!
That monster
Natuo treats you like cattle,
and you still do his dirty work.
Can you face your brothers
who died last night?
What are you standing around for?
Kill him!
Follow me.
You won't be slaves
in this mine anymore.
You'll all have a share
in this mine.
♪The bonds we forged stay in my heart♪
♪Plots and schemes are everywhere♪
What, you scared to fight?
Kill him now!
♪So what if fate mocks me?♪
♪This fight will defy fate itself♪
Fellow miners.
From now on, we follow Mian.
Mian!
Boss, things have changed.
Fall back.
Mian!
The brothers from the Blaze Gang
have been following me.
They've had nowhere to stay.
They've been living rough.
I want them settled here.
You're really making yourself
at home.
My miners are now your men.
What's next?
Don't tell me you're taking
my mine too.
It's your mine to begin with.
Why would I take it from you?
It's fine.
As long as you're mine,
what's mine is yours.
(I wonder how Mona's doing
with the evidence.)
Don't worry.
They're gone.
Come help me find the ledger.
I checked Natuo, Dashan,
and Suowen's accounts.
Thirty percent of their monthly income
was sent to an anonymous account.
Thirty percent?
That's their tribute to Mian.
You search here first.
Hey.
Found it.
This is it.
Thirty percent again.
Look.
I can't read this.
I forgot.
Let me.
This account
has transactions with Natuo's
other accounts.
Based on these transactions,
it looks like all the money
went to Grand Royal.
Grand Royal?
So that's where they pay tribute
to Mian.
Looks like we'll have to
visit Grand Royal ourselves.
Dad.
Why did you hand the mine
over to that woman, Layla?
Are you so sick you've lost your mind?
Watch your mouth.
She's your stepmother.
You're always acting crazy.
That's no way for a family head to act.
How can I trust you to run the group?
But I'm your son.
So what?
Ever since I gave you the mine,
you've been acting recklessly.
I won't sit by
and watch you squander
everything I built.
From now on, keep yourself
in check.
Do as your stepmother says.
I'm still calling you Dad
because this is your last chance.
Take back your decision,
and I'll let you live.
You're insane.
I'm your father!
So what?
If you support me,
you're my dad.
Otherwise,
you're just an old geezer.
Do you really think
your paralysis
was just an accident?
What did you say?
That crash five years ago,
I was the one
who had Jia cause it.
(You're taking forever.)
(What are you doing?)
(I've been waiting forever.)
It was never an accident.
You ungrateful son.
I'm your father.
When you trusted outsiders
and turned on me,
you should've seen this coming.
You were lucky to survive.
But all these years,
I waited for you to beg me
to take care of you till the end.
I waited for you to wise up.
You ungrateful son.
You ungrateful brat!
Why do you insist on
walking right into the blade?
♪Dust rises along the border♪
♪Out here, life and death are routine♪
♪Spent shells fall, last echoes ring♪
♪Brothers yesterday, foes today♪
♪Fate's blade falls, who can stop it?♪
♪Against the tide, I never bow♪
♪The night is long, the road unclear♪
♪My life is mine to bear♪
♪In chaos, a bloodied titan rages♪
♪I crush the thorns and reach the dawn♪
♪I fight back from death on all fronts♪
♪My fate is mine to command♪
♪Who dares stand in my way?♪
♪I weave through storms of bullets♪
♪I fight through flashing blades♪
♪Blood stains the whole land red♪
♪The bonds we forged stay in my heart♪
♪Plots and schemes are everywhere♪
♪Deceit runs deep, hard to see through♪
♪Every step is planned. I won't retreat♪
♪A spark ignites in the dark♪
♪So what if fate mocks me?♪
♪This fight will defy fate itself♪
♪Break every shackle, break every lock♪
♪Anger burns inside my chest♪
♪No more fear, no more losing my way♪
♪With blood and sweat, I forge my glory♪
♪In this world of chaos,
I carve out a road to brighter days♪
♪My legend, I'll write
every chapter myself♪
♪In chaos, a bloodied titan rages♪
♪I crush the thorns and reach the dawn♪
♪I fight back from death on all fronts♪
♪My fate is mine to command.
Who dares stand in my way?♪